batkhela.com 2005-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Batkhela.com

| 

Main Categories: 

  * Home Page
  * Islamic World
  * Display Pics
  * Pashto Music
  * Funny Pictures
  * MSN Emotions
  * Play Games
  * World of MSN
  * Greeting Cards
  * Funny Jokes
  * Join the Community
  * Free Wallpapers

General Sections: 

  * Photos Gallery
  * Link to us
  * Check E-Mail
  * Webmasters Tips
  * Guests Book
  * Privacy Policy
  * Contact Us

   |    
  Privacy Policy: 

First of all Thank you very much for visiting Batkhela.com  
Protecting your personal privacy is very important to us, Batkhela.com collects no personal information about you other than that which you choose to provide when you have questions or need help with a particular issue. Our server logs are used for administration purposes only and not shared with or available to any outside source. No individual identifying or personal information (such as your name) is automatically gathered when you visit Any Page of Batkhela.com, 

Batkhela.com has links to other useful sites on the Internet. Batkhela.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Batkhela.com has an online web form which you can use to contact us with questions on issues or problems, We use this information only to contact you about the matter of interest and to provide casework assistance.

Email addresses used in sending greeting cards, songs, wallpapers or other services are maintained only in the files containing the information These are not available to anyone beyond the webmaster in or outside of our organization.

Contact Us, if you have any question regarding this statement:  
  
Click here to Contact with us!

«

Back to Batkhela.com  

---|---
